<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sessions on</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/sessions/</link><description>Recent content in Sessions on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-1/</guid><description>Session 1 Innadel or Leradel Arrived at Innadel Met Breeze Went to the local tavern and question Breeze who was suspicious Archie notices guards outside the church Qidan scouts as a Bat We go and investigate FOR NO REASON EXCEPT NOSY Hostage situation Big fight Find letter with Black Seal with a monkey on From The Syndicate initiating the church into the fold Told to meet at Badger Hill Go to Badger Hill Get trapped by Lady Xiao CLIFFHANGER</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-2/</guid><description>Session 2 Badger Hill mages start filling the holes with CloudKill
Rescue the hippogriffs and Percival moonfluff beaky prometheus cloudfleather Big battle on Badger Hill
On the bodies found necklace diamond shape green gem in the center used for spell channeling.
Archibald maims La Qua La Qua
I am just following orders &amp;ldquo;You were asking questions about where she is from&amp;rdquo; RE: Lady Xiao If you take me with you I will get you into her Mansion We kill him</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-3/</guid><description>Session 3 Fang - used crystal, lasted for a week, but wolfkin had gone when he had got back
Reigning lady of Mitts High tea society fleeing - covered in dust - to the south
Ghost rebellion - mousekin and wolfkin kicked out - attempting to retake the city. An army (all) led by General Howlington
I ARRIVED LATE
Travelling to Ofheise On travelling we view a tear caused by the multi fang Fangs mom is at Ghost ready to attack Qidan dreams of a woman (believed to be Lady Ravana ) in all red who attempts to attack him Arrive at Ofheise Buys some shoes Go to the local tavern to find out about Lady Xiao Talks about Rauthei and a delivery from a rabbit person Archi got a tattoo Went to the stables Daria made the stable boy Qidan made friends with the horse Horse info - Lady Xiao has a a tail which is long and thin and can pick up items Fight on the bridge against zombies Met Murray Destroyer of Worlds which can talk</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-4/</guid><description>Session 4 Questioning Murray Destroyer of Worlds Attacked by Zombie lake boys Daria turns into a red mist after nearly dying mainly to friendly fire &amp;ldquo;you are in my domain&amp;rdquo; - CROW AND RAT unsure if they are in the same voice A wall of flesh fight Met a Wolfkin fighting, he said he can lead us to The Matron Daria intimidated Rico who is a Wolfkin warrior Met General Howlington Older Fang has a big EGO and has headed to fight The Marquis against the General&amp;rsquo;s orders</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-5/</guid><description>Session 5 We are gonna attack Dark Haven and get fang back &amp;ldquo;by Gorm yes&amp;rdquo; We need to make a alliance with the Vampires in Bathumhold (The Du Pontif&amp;rsquo;s ) to attack Dark Haven Old Wolf - Small Hovel, in Ellingville Quag, supply crates have gone missing which has health potions in Head to Bathumhold with Twink Wolfkin scout, no name needed he is too cute Travel through the tunnel Walrus fight.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-6/</guid><description>Session 6 Questioning rico about the sniper It is from Ofheise (maybe there is a bang stick shop there?) Going after the wolfkin deserters who are in Murkwood Pincer fish in river technique Wolfkin party found, one fully dressed and the others are in there underwolfwear Wolfkin turned out to be werewolves!!! Qidan turns 2 of them back to wolfkin using Moonbean and now they are going to be followers of Hoar going to the temple that Daria is from NOTHING BAD CAN COME FROM THIS.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-7/</guid><description>Session 7 Dominus Oraculum number 3 came true Get a phoenix circlet Everyone wants to sell it I want it We get 30 Wolves We get 10 Vampire Total Cost 1.8 G Archi Lore dump on Myts as we travel to Myts Myts lost every fight Thinning of the vial which causes un-natural effects with spell casters On Marpenoth 20, 1381 at 13:04:25, duck.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-8/</guid><description>Session 8 After the murder of Lady Xiao
Daria
Went back to the slums She monitored the local tarvern to see if any authorities come Barricades and blimps monitor the city of Myts The door of the tavern opens and closes Winter
Ran back to the tarvern Qidan
Went to ground and got high Tried to send a message - Failed Archi
Found Breeze in the Chapel</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-9/</guid><description>Session 9 Go Back to breeze Attacked by Assassins which breeze suggested he should leave and he did. WE FORGOT THE NOTE the assassin left. Breeze was attacked by the Assassin and we escape from the returning suggested Assassin using the Pigeon Winch (Wench) We killed a child (the one in the bag of holding) Daria wanted to havest the organs Qidan is distraught Have to travel pass all the the guards which we do amazingly using innate disguise self Get back to the slums where the butcher and the stable boy is locking their door /SUS/, We go to the Stable boy and get admitted into the Stables where we can rest.</description></item><item><title>Session 10</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-10/</guid><description>Rave 1 v 1 (Daria Vs Romanof) Daria fucking owned Romanof She is so broken&amp;hellip; Romanof says he will clear the West side of the wall at Sunset Melon Orgy The poet is melon inspired from the melon orgy and is writting sonnets and odes to melon. The Attack on Minster Rabniar&amp;rsquo;s House The Attack to escape Myts happened two fold. Winter Daira and Qidan Archi Winter, Daira and Qidan At the west side of the wall, all use disguse self to turn into a trio of maids:</description></item><item><title>Session 11</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-11/</guid><description>Session 11 Waking up in the desert RING RING its you Motorola Sending Stone Breeze and other have arrived and will be made to work for there keep Myts first regiment has been mobilised for Archi Plots many ways to kill them Using our Vampire and Werewolf army Taking over the prison and trap them Avoiding them all We still need to talk about this Talking about hopes lament Rumour of the woman in black arriving at the prison and taking over in a blink of a eye.</description></item></channel></rss>