<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sessions on</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/sessions/</link><description>Recent content in Sessions on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Session 1</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-1/</guid><description>Session 1 Innadel or Leradel Arrived at Innadel Met Breeze Went to the local tavern and question Breeze who was suspicious Archie notices guards outside the church Qidan scouts as a Bat We go and investigate FOR NO REASON EXCEPT NOSY Hostage situation Big fight Find letter with Black Seal with a monkey on From The Syndicate initiating the church into the fold Told to meet at Badger Hill Go to Badger Hill Get trapped by Lady Xiao CLIFFHANGER</description></item><item><title>Session 10</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-10/</guid><description>Session 10 Rave 1 v 1 (Daria Vs Romanof) Daria fucking owned Romanof She is so broken&amp;hellip; Romanof says he will clear the West side of the wall at Sunset Melon Orgy The poet is melon inspired from the melon orgy and is writting sonnets and odes to melon.</description></item><item><title>Session 11</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-11/</guid><description>Session 11 Waking up in the desert RING RING its you Motorola Sending Stone Breeze and other have arrived and will be made to work for there keep Myts first regiment has been mobilised for Archi Plots many ways to kill them Using our Vampire and Werewolf army Taking over the prison and trap them Avoiding them all We still need to talk about this Talking about hopes lament Rumour of the woman in black arriving at the prison and taking over in a blink of a eye.</description></item><item><title>Session 12</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-12/</guid><description>Session 12 In the Warden&amp;rsquo;s Office and on to PorkyPorcus We have been there for a while, I remained as a rat while the other members of the party tried to be all big boss scary.</description></item><item><title>Session 13</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-13/</guid><description>Session 13 I was delierious from Covid so my notes may not be as complete.
Battle of Porkus and the Searching the Room So we do the deed, notable point Daria is blinded during the battle but still cannot be hit and takes out two dogs in the process.</description></item><item><title>Session 14</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-14/</guid><description>Session 14 I didnt write too much for this so I am going off memory. I got distracted by all the romance in the air.</description></item><item><title>Session 2</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-2/</guid><description>Session 2 Badger Hill mages start filling the holes with CloudKill
Rescue the hippogriffs and Percival</description></item><item><title>Session 3</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-3/</guid><description>Session 3 Fang - used crystal, lasted for a week, but wolfkin had gone when he had got back
Reigning lady of Mitts High tea society fleeing - covered in dust - to the south</description></item><item><title>Session 4</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-4/</guid><description>Session 4 Questioning Morie Destroyer of Worlds Attacked by Zombie lake boys Daria turns into a red mist after nearly dying mainly to friendly fire &amp;ldquo;you are in my domain&amp;rdquo; - CROW AND RAT unsure if they are in the same voice A wall of flesh fight Met a Wolfkin fighting, he said he can lead us to The Matron Daria intimidated Rico who is a Wolfkin warrior Met General Howlington Older Fang has a big EGO and has headed to fight The Marquis against the General&amp;rsquo;s orders</description></item><item><title>Session 5</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-5/</guid><description>Session 5 We are gonna attack Dark Haven and get fang back &amp;ldquo;by Gorm yes&amp;rdquo; We need to make a alliance with the Vampires in Bathumhold (The Du Pontif&amp;rsquo;s) to attack Dark Haven Old Wolf - Small Hovel, in Ellingville Quag, supply crates have gone missing which has health potions in Head to Bathumhold with Twink Wolfkin scout, no name needed he is too cute Travel through the tunnel Walrus fight.</description></item><item><title>Session 6</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-6/</guid><description>Session 6 Questioning rico about the sniper It is from Ofheise (maybe there is a bang stick shop there?</description></item><item><title>Session 7</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-7/</guid><description>Session 7 Dominus Oraculum number 3 came true Get a phoenix circlet Everyone wants to sell it I want it We get 30 Wolves We get 10 Vampire Total Cost 1.</description></item><item><title>Session 8</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-8/</guid><description>Session 8 After the murder of Lady Xiao
Daria
Went back to the slums She monitored the local tarvern to see if any authorities come Barricades and blimps monitor the city of Myts The door of the tavern opens and closes Winter</description></item><item><title>Session 9</title><link>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j0nesma.github.io/quartz/Sessions/Session-9/</guid><description>Session 9 Go Back to breeze Attacked by Assassins which breeze suggested he should leave and he did. WE FORGOT THE NOTE the assassin left.</description></item></channel></rss>